Guide to the Tamiment Library Poster and Broadside Collection GRAPHICS.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: United States, undated
  - United States: Marxist-Leninist Party, undated; US-128.0; 4 items (Box Shared Tamiment OS003)
    Feminism; China; Mao, Zedong, 1893-1976
  - United States: May Day, undated; US-34.0; 24 items (Flat-file-folder 7 Left)
    Unemployment.; Puerto Rico.; Iran.; Labor unions; Revolutionary Communist Youth Brigade (U.S.); Revolutionary Communist Party, USA; Vietnam Veterans Against the War; Gellert, Hugo, 1892-1985; Iranian Students Association of America
  - United States: About Mexico, undated; US-81.0; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - United States: About Middle East, undated; US-35.0; 4 items (Flat-file-folder 8 Left)
    Iran.
  - United States: Motion Pictures, undated; US-26.0; 19 items (Flat-file-folder 9)
    Student movements.; Labor unions; Draft resisters.; Chile.; Health; El Salvador.; Performances.; Black power.; Mozambique.; Iran.; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Labor Theater (New York, N.Y.); Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives; AFL-CIO
  - United States: Music, undated; US-36.0; 22 items (Flat-file-folder 11)
    Chile.; Health; Labor unions; El Salvador.; China; Central America.; Cuba.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
  - United States: Native Americans, undated; US-37.0; 17 items (Flat-file-folder 7 Left)
    Portraits.; Prisoners and prisons.; American Indian Movement
  - United States: New American Movement, undated; US-122.0; 2 items (Box 2)
    Feminism; Socialism
  - United States: New York State Labor History Association, undated; US-105.0; 4 items (Box 2)
  - United States: Occupational Safety and Health, undated; US-39.0; 6 items (Box 1)
    Health; Labor unions; Prisoners and prisons.; Civil rights.; Transport Workers Union of America; AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council
  - United States: About Oman, undated; US-120.0; 7 items (Box 2)
    Iranian Students Association of America
  - United States: About Palestine, undated; US-40.0; 2 items (Box 1)
  - United States: Peace and Freedom Party, undated; US-98.0; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 11 Right)
    Political campaigns.; Black power.
  - United States: Performances, undated; US-52.0; 41 items (Flat-file-folder 5 Left)
    Prisoners and prisons.; Student movements.; Black power.; Disarmament.; South Africa; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Health; Socialism; México.; France.; Women employees.; Civil rights.; Labor unions; Industrial safety.; Randolph, A. Philip (Asa Philip), 1889-1979; Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee (U.S.); Mandela, Nelson, 1918-2013; Coalition for a Nuclear-Free Harbor (New York, N.Y.); Congress of Racial Equality; Gellert, Hugo, 1892-1985; National Association for the Advancement of Colored People; San Francisco Mime Troupe
  - United States: Performances - The Labor Theater, undated; US-52.1; 18 items (Box 1)
    Health; Socialism; Music.; Labor unions; Industrial safety.; Women employees.; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); Industrial Workers of the World
  - United States: About Philippines, undated; US-43.0; 1 item (Box 1)
  - United States: Portraits, undated; US-76.0; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 12 Right)
    Cuba.; Germany (West); Luxemburg, Rosa, 1871-1919; Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924; New American Movement (Organization); Castro, Fidel, 1926-2016
  - United States: Prisons and Prisoners, undated; US-44.0; 3 items (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
    Puerto Rico.; Draft resisters.; Student movements.; Black power.; Indians of North America.; Black Panther Party; Attica Defense Committee
  - United States: Progressive Labor Party, undated; US-121.0; 2 items (Box 2)
    Socialism; May Day.
  - United States: Promotional (Books, Periodicals, Games and Other Items), undated; US-102.0; 15 items (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    Labor unions; Anarchism.; South Africa
  - United States: Public Transportation, undated; US-114.0; 3 items (Flat-file-folder 9)
    Labor unions; Transport Workers Union of America
  - United States: About Puerto Rico, undated; US-46.0; 22 items (Flat-file-folder 5)
    Feminism; Prisoners and prisons.; Civil rights.; Junta de Coordinación Revolucionaria del Cono Sur; Partido Socialista Puertorriqueño; Movimiento de Izquierda Revolucionaria (Chile); Movimiento de Liberación Nacional (Uruguay)
  - United States: Rand School, undated; US-47.0; 1 item (Box 1)
  - United States: Reproductive Rights, undated; US-48.0; 5 items (Flat-file-folder 15 Right)
    International Women's Day.
  - United States: Revolutionary Communist Party, undated; US-126.0; 2 items (Box 2)
  - United States: Revolutionary Student Brigade, undated; US-124.0; 6 items (Box 2)
    Student movements.; Music.; South Africa
  - United States: Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, undated; US-104.0; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    Labor unions; AFL-CIO
  - United States: Rosenberg Case, undated; US-82.0; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    Civil rights.
  - United States: Schools, undated; US-49.0; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 6 Left)
    Student movements.
  - United States: Schools--Community School Board, New York City, undated; US-49.2; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 4)
    Children's rights.
  - United States: Social Classes, undated; US-140.0; 3 items (Flat-file-folder 8)
  - United States: Socialism, undated; US-100.0; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
    United Kingdom.; Black power.; Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968; Intercollegiate Socialist Society (U.S.); Hardie, James Keir, 1856-1915
  - United States: Socialist Party, undated; US-112.0; 13 items (Flat-file-folder 10)
    Political campaigns.; Labor unions; Prisoners and prisons.; Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968; Workmen's Circle (U.S.); London, Meyer, 1871-1926; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Debs, Eugene V. (Eugene Victor), 1855-1926
  - United States: About Spain, undated; US-64.0; 1 item (Box 1)
  - United States: Spanish Civil War, undated; US-50.0; 2 items (Box 1)
  - United States: Student Protest, undated; US-109.0; 16 items (Flat-file-folder 11)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; France.
  - United States: Student Protest - New York University Student Strike, undated; US-109.2; 18 items (Box 2)
    Political campaigns.; Labor unions; Black power.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; South Africa; Black Panther Party
  - United States: Student Protest - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), undated; US-109.1; 6 items (Box 2)
    Civil rights.; Feminism; Political campaigns.; Black power.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Prisoners and prisons.; Students for a Democratic Society (U.S.)
  - United States: Trotskyism, undated; US-136.0; 1 item (Box Shared Tamiment OS003)
  - United States: Unemployment, undated; US-107.0; 6 items (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
    World War, 1939-1945.; Labor unions
  - United States: Union Label, undated; US-53.0; 4 items (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - United States: Vietnam War (opposition to), undated; US-11.0; 49 items (Flat-file-folder 1)
    Civil rights.; Labor unions; Bolivia.; Black power.; Portraits.; South America.; Uruguay.; Student movements.; Cambodia.; Chile.; Puerto Rico.; Political campaigns.; Prisoners and prisons.; Health; Central America.; Black Panther Party; Youth Against War & Fascism; Vietnam Veterans Against the War; Ho, Chí Minh, 1890-1969; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968; Movimiento de Izquierda Revolucionaria (Chile); National Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam; Junta de Coordinación Revolucionaria del Cono Sur; Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam; Movimiento de Liberación Nacional (Uruguay)
  - United States: Vietnam War (support for), undated; US-11.1; 2 items (Box 1)
  - United States: Voting, undated; US-138.0; 1 item (Box 2)
  - United States: Women Workers, undated; US-55.0; 10 items (Flat-file-folder 8 Right)
    Labor unions; 9 to 5, National Association of Working Women (U.S.); Meany, George, 1894-1980; AFL-CIO
  - United States: Women Workers - Labor Unions, undated; US-55.1; 4 items (Box 1)
    Boycotts.; Feminism; United Farm Workers of America; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.)
  - United States: Women's Movement, undated; US-56.0; 47 items (Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder Shared Tamiment 112)
    Equal rights amendments; South America.; Black power.; Performances.; Exhibitions.; Ireland.; Disarmament.; Women employees.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Women's International League for Peace and Freedom; Truth, Sojourner, 1799-1883; Tubman, Harriet, 1822-1913
  - United States: Women's Movement - International Women's Day, undated; US-56.1; 14 items (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
    Women employees.; China; Iran.; New American Movement (Organization); October League (M-L)
  - United States: Women's Movement - Reconstruction Women's Graphic Collective, circa late 20th century (Folder Shared Tamiment 109)
  - United States: Women's Movement - Violence Against Women, undated; US-56.3; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
  - United States: Workers Party, undated; US-132.0; 1 item (Box 2)
    Political campaigns.; Foster, William Z., 1881-1961; Cannon, James Patrick, 1890-1974
  - United States: World War II, undated; US-57.0; 11 items (Flat-file-folder 8)
    Jews.; Poland; Housing.; Shahn, Ben, 1898-1969
  - United States: Young Peoples Socialist League (YPSL), undated; US-131.0; 2 items (Box Shared Tamiment OS003)
    Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968
  - United States: Young Socialist Alliance, undated; US-123.0; 4 items (Flat-file-folder 9 Left)
    Black power.; Cuba.; Student movements.; France.; X, Malcolm, 1925-1965
  - United States: Youth Internation Party (YIPPIE), undated; US-108.0; 13 items (Flat-file-folder 5)
    Political campaigns.; Marijuana.
  - United States: Strikes, General, undated; US-51.0 (Box 1)
    Labor unions; Industrial Workers of the World
  - United States: Revolution, 1968-1971 (Box 1)
- Series II: Other Countries, undated
  - Angola: General, undated; AO-2.0; 6 items (Box 2)
    Movimento Popular de Libertação de Angola
  - Argentina: General, undated; AR-60.0; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Australia: General, undated; AU-93.0; 1 item (Box 2)
    World War, 1939-1945.
  - Austria: General, undated; AT-94.0; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 12 Right)
    Socialism; World War, 1939-1945.; Cuba.; Germany (West)
  - Belgium: General, undated; BE-119.0; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 3)
    Feminism
  - Brazil: General, undated; BR-15.0; 11 items (Flat-file-folder 15 Right)
    Prisoners and prisons.; Industrial safety.; Housing.; Labor unions
  - Canada: Non-Canadian topics, undated; CA-85.1; 12 items (Flat-file-folder 13 Right)
    Zimbabwe.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Angola.; Philippines.; Mozambique.; Boycotts.; United Farm Workers of America; Ho, Chí Minh, 1890-1969
  - Chile: General, undated; CL-17.3; 10 items (Flat-file-folder 11 Right)
    Prisoners and prisons.
  - Chile: United Popular Action Movement (Movimiento de Acción Popular Unitario (MAPU)), undated; CL-17.0; 6 items (Flat-file-folder 14 Right)
  - China, People's Republic of: China: General, undated; CN-42.0; 152 items (Flat-file-folder 16 Right, Flat-file-folder 17 Right, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4)
    Soviet Union.; Portraits.; Performances.; Women employees.; Schools.; Health; Mao, Zedong, 1893-1976; Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924
  - China, People's Republic of: Non-Chinese topics, undated; CN-42.1; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
    South America.; Central America.
  - China, People's Republic of: Portraits, undated; CN-76.0; 8 items (Box 2)
    Soviet Union.; Marx, Karl, 1818-1883; Engels, Friedrich, 1820-1895; Stalin, Joseph, 1878-1953; Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924
  - Cuba: General, undated; CU-21.0; 17 items (Flat-file-folder 8)
    Portraits.; May Day.; Exhibitions.; Socialism; International Women's Day.; Disarmament.; Engels, Friedrich, 1820-1895; Castro, Fidel, 1926-2016; Marx, Karl, 1818-1883
  - Cuba: Non-Cuban topics, undated; CU-21.1; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 5 Left)
    Puerto Rico.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Prisoners and prisons.; Ho, Chí Minh, 1890-1969
  - Cuba: Poster produced by Departamento de Orientación Revolucionaria, undated (Flat-file-folder 1 Right)
  - Cuba: Posters produced by Organizacion de la Solaridad de los Pueblos de Africa, Asis y Latinoamerica (OSPAAL) about Africa, undated; CU-21.4; 8 items (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    Zimbabwe.; Angola.; Mozambique.
  - Cuba: Posters produced by Organizacion de la Solaridad de los Pueblos de Africa, Asis y Latinoamerica (OSPAAL) about miscellaneous subjects., undated; CU-21.3; 26 items (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
    Puerto Rico.; Black power.; Nicaragua.; Guinea-Bissau.; Middle East.; El Salvador.; Dominican Republic.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Venezuela.; Uruguay.; Prisoners and prisons.; Cuba.; Ho, Chí Minh, 1890-1969; Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional
  - Cuba: Posters produced by Organization Continental Latinoamericana de Estudiantes (OCLAE) on miscellaneous topics, undated; CU-21.2; 12 items (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Uruguay.; Perú.; Chile.; Angola.; Student movements.; Prisoners and prisons.; Cuba.; Puerto Rico.
  - Czechoslovakia: Produced by International Union of Students on other topics, undated; CS-66.1; 48 items (Flat-file-folder 7 Left)
    Ireland.; Guinea-Bissau.; Indochina.; South Korea.; Chile.; Paraguay.; Disarmament.; Prisoners and prisons.; Cuba.; Portugal.; Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924
  - Czechoslovakia: About Africa, undated; CS-1.0; 25 items (Flat-file-folder 8 Left)
    Mozambique.; Ethiopia.; Zimbabwe.; Madagascar.; South Africa; Student movements.; Namibia.; Angola.; Oman.; Prisoners and prisons.; Algeria.; Cameroon.; Movimento Popular de Libertação de Angola; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: About Caribbean, undated; CS-62.0; 9 items (Flat-file-folder 6 Left)
    Cuba.; Dominican Republic.; Haiti; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: About Central America, undated; CS-73.0; 5 items (Box 2)
    Nicaragua.; Prisoners and prisons.; Guatemala.; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: About Columbia, undated; CS-90.0; 6 items (Box 2)
    Prisoners and prisons.; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: About Mexico, undated; CS-81.0; 4 items (Box 2)
  - Czechoslovakia: About Morocco, undated; CS-91.0; 6 items (Box 2)
  - Czechoslovakia: About Palestine, undated; CS-40.0; 6 items (Box 2)
    Israel.
  - Czechoslovakia: About Panama, undated; CS-61.0; 6 items (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
    Student movements.; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: About the Middle East, undated; CS-35.0; 12 items (Box 2)
    Lebanon.; Jordan.; Cyprus.; Prisoners and prisons.; Saudi Arabia; Iraq.; Israel.; Iran.; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: Miscellaneous non-Czechoslovakian topics, undated; CS-134.1; 6 items (Flat-file-folder 10)
    May Day.; World Federation of Democratic Youth
  - Czechoslovakia: Produced by International Union of Students about International Union of Students-sponsored events, undated; CS-66.0; 39 items (Flat-file-folder 9)
    Middle East.; Egypt.; Disarmament.; Student movements.; Germany (West); Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924
  - Czechoslovakia: About Puerto Rico, undated; CS-46.0; 5 items (Flat-file-folder 11 Right)
  - Czechoslovakia: About South America, undated; CS-111.0; 18 items (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
    Paraguay.; Brazil.; Bolivia.; Venezuela.; Argentina.; Chile.; Prisoners and prisons.; International Union of Students
  - Czechoslovakia: About Sudan, undated; CS-67.0; 9 items (Box 1)
  - Czechoslovakia: About Vietnam, undated; CS-11.0; 14 items (Flat-file-folder 9 Right)
    Health; International Union of Students
  - Denmark: Denmark, non-Danish topics, undated; DK-80.1; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 14 Right)
  - Denmark: General, undated; DK-80.0; 3 items (Flat-file-folder 3)
    Feminism; Exhibitions.
  - Dominican Republic: General, undated; DO-75.0; 1 item (Box 2)
    International Women's Day.; Women employees.
  - El Salvador: General, undated; SV-23.0; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 14 Right)
    Frente Farabundo Martí para la Liberación Nacional
  - El Salvador: Non-Salvadorean topics, undated; SV-23.1; 1 item (Box 2)
    May Day.
  - Finland: General, undated; FI-86.0; 4 items (Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
    Disarmament.; World Peace Council
  - France: Communist Party, undated; FR-20.0; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - France: General, undated; FR-96.0; 11 items (Flat-file-folder 1)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Disarmament.
  - France: Non-French topics, undated; FR-96.1; 4 items (Flat-file-folder 5)
    Disarmament.; Portraits.; Confederación Nacional del Trabajo (Spain); International Union of Students; Unión General de Trabajadores de España; Marx, Karl, 1818-1883; World Federation of Democratic Youth
  - German Democratic Republic (East Germany): Non-East German topics, undated; DD-129.1; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 5 Left)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975.
  - German Federal Republic (West Germany): Non-West-German topics, undated; DE-63.1; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - German Federal Republic (West Germany): General, undated; DE-63.0; 12 items (Flat-file-folder 6)
    Jews.; Unemployment.; Performances.; Disarmament.; Socialism; Labor unions; International Women's Day.; Schools.; Portraits.; Luxemburg, Rosa, 1871-1919; Crane, Walter, 1845-1915; Sozialistischer Deutscher Studentenbund; Kommunistische Partei Deutschlands; Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands; Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924; Marx, Karl, 1818-1883
  - Greece: General, undated; GR-68.0; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Guatemala: General, undated; GT-58.0; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 13 Right)
  - Hungary: Non-Hungarian Topics, undated; HU-133.1; 1 item (Box 2)
    World Federation of Trade Unions
  - Hungary: Posters Produced by World Federation of Democratic Youth on miscellaneous topics, undated; HU-92.1; 3 items (Box 2)
    Chile.; South Africa
  - Ireland: General, undated; IE-70.0; 2 items (Box 2)
    Ireland.; Prisoners and prisons.
  - Ireland: Non-Irish topics, undated; IE-70.1; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 15 Right)
  - Italy: General, undated; IT-79.0; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 12 Right, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Japan: Disarmament, undated; JP-59.0; 17 items (Flat-file-folder 11 Right)
  - Mexico: General, undated; MX-81.0; 5 items (Flat-file-folder 2)
    May Day.; Portraits.; Internationalist Workers Party (Fourth International); Zapata, Emiliano, 1879-1919; Trotsky, Leon, 1879-1940
  - Mexico: Non-Mexican topics, undated; MX-81.1; 4 items (Flat-file-folder 13 Right)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975.; Women employees.; Nicaragua.; World Federation of Trade Unions
  - Mozambique: About, and produced by, Frente de Liberta√ß√£o de Mo√ßambique (FRELIMO, aka Liberation Front of Mozambique), undated; MZ-3.0; 4 items (Box 2)
  - Mozambique: General, undated; MZ-3.2; 18 items (Flat-file-folder 12 Right)
    Portugal.
  - Netherlands: Non-Dutch topics, undated; NL-89.1; 4 items (Box 2)
    Mozambique.; Namibia.; Angola.; SWAPO; Movimento Popular de Libertação de Angola
  - New Zealand: Labor Unions, undated; NZ-54.0; 8 items (Box 2)
    Women employees.; Industrial safety.
  - Nicaragua: General, undated; NI-38.0; 38 items (Flat-file-folder 10 Right)
    Feminism; May Day.; Central America.; Schools.; CST (Organization)
  - Nicaragua: Nicaragua Conflict - Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional (aka FSLN, aka Sandinista National Liberation Front), undated; NI-38.2; 20 items (Flat-file-folder 7 Left)
    AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council
  - Nicaragua: Set of posters Commemorating General Sandino, undated; NI-38.4; 20 items (Flat-file-folder 1 Left)
    Exhibitions.; Central America.
  - Nicaragua: Set of posters: "The Path of Nicaragua" produced by Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional (aka FSLN, aka Sandinista National Liberation Front), undated; NI-38.3; 15 items (Box 2)
    Schools.; Health; Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional
  - Panama: General, undated; PA-61.0; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 3 Left)
  - Paraguay: General, undated; PY-41.0; 1 item (Flat-file-folder 6 Left)
  - Poland: General, undated; PL-97.0; 3 items (Flat-file-folder 13)
    Disarmament.; Labor unions; World Federation of Trade Unions; World Peace Council
  - Portugal: General, undated; PT-71.0; 5 items (Flat-file-folder 14)
    Feminism; Prisoners and prisons.; Argentina.; Labor unions; International-Communist League; Movimento de Esquerda Socialista; F. S. P.
  - Singapore: General, undated; SG-87.0; 1 item (Box 2)
  - South Africa: General, undated; ZA-5.0; 1 item (Box Shared Tamiment OS003)
  - Spain: General, undated; ES-64.0; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 8 Left)
    Labor unions; Unión General de Trabajadores de España
  - Spain: Spanish Civil War, undated; ES-50.0; 35 items
    May Day.; Schools.; Anarchism.; Federación Internacional de Juventudes Libertarias; International Workers Association; Partido Obrero de Unificación Marxista; F.A.I. (Organization: Spain); Confederación Nacional del Trabajo (Spain); Unión General de Trabajadores de España
  - Spain: C.N.T. Un Marino: Un Heroe, Undated; cuid888; 1 item one poster (Item GRAPHICS.002.cuid888)
    Scope and Contents
    Artist: Arturo Ballester
    Posters.
  - Sweden: General, undated; SE-88.0; 7 items (Flat-file-folder 11)
    Arbetaren
  - Sweden: Non-Swedish topics, undated; SE-88.1; 2 items (Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR): Communist Party of USSR, undated; SU-20.0; 22 items (Flat-file-folder 16)
    Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR): Communist Party of USSR, Educational Set, undated; SU-20.3; 16 items (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR): General, undated; SU-95.0; 13 items (Flat-file-folder 15)
    Disarmament.; Portraits.; Sovetskiĭ komitet zashchity mira; Lenin, Vladimir Il'ich, 1870-1924; Marx, Karl, 1818-1883
  - United Kingdom: Labour Party, undated; GB-84.0; 41 items (Flat-file-folder 1 Left, Flat-file-folder 8)
    Unemployment.; Exhibitions.; Labor unions; Disarmament.; Political campaigns.; Anarchism.; Feminism; MacDonald, James Ramsay, 1866-1937; Peace Pledge Union
  - United Kingdom: Labour Party--"To-morrow When Labour Rules", undated; GB-84.0-4 (Folder Shared Tamiment 109)
    40 x 60
  - United Kingdom: Miscellaneous political topics (produced by one unidentified organization), undated; GB-84.3; 90 items (Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
    Central America.; Schools.; Exhibitions.; France.; Unemployment.; Zimbabwe.; Philippines.; Student movements.; South America.; China; International Women's Day.; Soviet Union.; Ireland.; Socialism; Labor unions; Black power.; Health; Chile.; Feminism; Anarchism.; Durruti, Buenaventura, 1896-1936; Mao, Zedong, 1893-1976; Ho, Chí Minh, 1890-1969
  - United Kingdom: General, undated; GB-84.0; 18 items (Flat-file-folder 7)
    Anarchist Black Cross; Peace Pledge Union
  - United Kingdom: Non-United Kingdom topics, undated; GB-84.1; 10 items (Flat-file-folder 3)
    Performances.; Socialism; Soviet Union.; Labor unions; Disarmament.; Namibia.; Chile.; Portraits.; Health; Portugal.; Nicaragua.; Anarchism.; SWAPO; Marx, Karl, 1818-1883; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.)
  - Holding Files, General, undated; HF-135.0 (Flat-file-folder 2)
- Color Transparencies (Box 10)